resartis.org 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy | ResArtis

**Introduction**

Res Artis takes your privacy and the protection of your personal data seriously and acts in accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

This Privacy Policy explains how personal information is collected, used, stored and disclosed by Res Artis. This Policy applies to Res Artis members and non-members. Our subscribed members share their professional identities, engage with our network, exchange knowledge and professional insights and post relevant professional profiles and residency opportunities. The content and data of some of our services is viewable to non-members.

By visiting or using the Res Artis website, you are consenting to us gathering and processing information about you in accordance with this Policy.

**What information does Res Artis collect?**

Res Artis collects the basic personal data that you provide to us in the form of your personal and/or professional contact information. We do not use online analytical tools, cookies or location tracking services.

In addition to the above, Res Artis members submit detailed data about their residency programs, including an annual operating budget and billing information. We use this financial information to uphold our tiered pricing system to enable an inclusive and diverse membership.

**Why does Res Artis need it and what do we do with it?**

Res Artis needs to collect basic personal data to provide you with communications about our activities. You must opt-in to our different communications channels, and have the right to subscribe, unsubscribe or update your subscription preferences at any time.

Res Artis requires more detailed information about our residency members in order to promote their organisation and residency opportunities to our international network and the public. All personal data captured by Res Artis has been submitted voluntarily by Res Artis members with their consent for public viewing and promotion across our various communications channels (see note about third party providers below).

**How do we capture it?**

The personal data we capture is processed by Res Artis staff. For the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance, this information is securely held. No third parties have access to your personal data unless you have otherwise consented (see note about third party providers below).

**How long do we keep it?**

Under Dutch law we are required to keep financial records for a minimum period of 7 years.

**What are your rights?**

If at any point you believe the personal data Res Artis captures about you is incorrect, you can contact Res Artis to request the information be amended or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint about the way Res Artis have handled your personal data, you can contact us:

Res Artis

Sarphatistraat 470  
1018 GW Amsterdam  
The Netherlands

**A note about third party service providers**

Res Artis makes use of third party service providers for our e-newsletters and social media communications. By consenting to receive these communications through our third party service providers, you are subject to their individual privacy policies, and Res Artis does not take any responsibility for how such third parties may use any personal data they collect. You can view the Privacy Policies of our third party service providers here:

**Changes to this Policy**

Res Artis reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy, and if we make material changes to it, will provide you with the opportunity to review the changes before they become effective. If you object to any changes, you may opt-out of Res Artis communications and/or membership.

_Last updated 23.05.2018_
